

CONTACT INFO



Karachi, Pakistán



+923363424021



Iusamarehman96gmail.com



github.com/iamusamarehman

LANGUAGE

English: Native

Urdu: Native

EXPERTISE

Tableau

Mixpanel

Google Analytics 360

Google Data Studio

Notion, Trello

Zendesk, Intercom

MORE ABOUT ME



Visit my online CV by scanning the QR code to learn more about me.

Usama Rehman

PHP/LARAVEL DEVELOPER

/javi

/usamarehman87



EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Web Developer specializing in back-end and front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. offering you two years of team-based application development experience. I consider myself to be a person who can solve problems creatively and take advantage of opportunities. Strong background

WORK EXPERIENCE

ECOMMERCE PRODUCT OWNER

02/2016 - Present

CongoBasin INC, Arlington County, VA

Employing over 1M people, CongoBasin is the largest online retailer in the world. At their Arlington, VA Hub, as a product owner for congobasin.co's Office Electronics department, I have led a multidisciplinary team of 20 software developers, UX designers, and data scientists.

ECOMMERCE PRODUCT OWNER

01/2014 - 02/2016

CongoBasin INC, Arlington County, VA

Employing over 1M people, CongoBasin is the largest online retailer in the world. At their Arlington, VA Hub, as a product owner for congobasin.co's Office Electronics department, I have led a multidisciplinary team of 20 software developers, UX designers, and data scientists.

ECOMMERCE PRODUCT OWNER

06/2011 - 01/2014

CongoBasin INC, Arlington County, VA

Employing over 1M people, CongoBasin is the largest online retailer in the world. At their Arlington, VA Hub, as a product owner for congobasin.co's Office Electronics department, I have led a multidisciplinary team of 20 software developers, UX designers, and data scientists.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Bachelor Of Software Engineering 2016-2021

Usman Institute of Technology Affilated NEDUET
Intermediate 2014-2016

Govt. College for Men

Matriculation 2012-2014

Millennium's Education System

CERTIFICATES

PMPs & CAPMs

Project Management Institute

SEARCH AND SHOPPING CAMPAIGNS

Google Ads